<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gip on GIP site</title>
    <link>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/tags/gip/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gip on GIP site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 14:46:35 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/tags/gip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Instructiefilmpje Sway Engels</title>
      <link>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/artikels/IT-tapa/InstructiefilmSwayENG/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 14:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/artikels/IT-tapa/InstructiefilmSwayENG/</guid>
      <description>&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/yXzof-j0bsY&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instructiefilmpje Sway Nederland</title>
      <link>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/artikels/IT-tapa/InstructiefilmSwayNL/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 14:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/artikels/IT-tapa/InstructiefilmSwayNL/</guid>
      <description>&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/EaHaAgpjdxk&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Middagsessie Sway</title>
      <link>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/artikels/IT-tapa/SwayMiddagsesssie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 14:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/artikels/IT-tapa/SwayMiddagsesssie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Onze, &lt;a href=&#34;http://ricardo-coenen.github.io/GIPsite/&#34;&gt;Ricardo&lt;/a&gt; en Jens, middagsessie ging over Sway. Sway is de opvolger van PowerPoint, en is veel gebruiksvriendelijker. Als je niet veel van PowerPoint kent, is Sway de ideale oplossing voor u. Als je echter veel van PowerPoint kent en je wilt veel creativiteit gebruiken is PowerPoint nog steeds de koploper. Sway is goed, maar omdat het net uit preview is loopt het vaak vast en je kunt Sway ook niet gebruiken wanneer je geen internet hebt. Het is dus geen programma maar iets in je browser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hier onder vind je ook onze facebook pagina en onze FAQ:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/IT-tapa-588405757863108/&#34;&gt;&lt;img height=&#34;50px&#34; src=&#34;https://encrypted-tbn2.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcT9MOS_pH3Z-5vif6J49GnlMsJgQBsVgxbzYfcEZYiWwAd4Sr5M&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://google.com.au/&#34;&gt;&lt;img height=&#34;50px&#34; src=&#34;http://icons.iconarchive.com/icons/icojam/blue-bits/256/question-faq-icon.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;400&#34;  src=&#34;https://scontent-ams2-1.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-xal1/t31.0-8/12240203_931268806910133_3764191703089532_o.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;400&#34; src=&#34;https://scontent-ams2-1.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-xpf1/t31.0-8/12247988_931268696910144_4134057028211480645_o.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT-autobiography</title>
      <link>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/artikels/Engels/IT-autobiography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 14:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/artikels/Engels/IT-autobiography/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My name is Jens Van Hoof, a 17-year old! student at the Immaculata institute in Oostmalle. Currently I&amp;rsquo;m studying IT-management. Most of the time, I&amp;rsquo;m the guy who helps people who don&amp;rsquo;t get it yet. Later I want to be a programmer of software or games. My dream job is to be a hacker for the state.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width=&#34;400px&#34; height=&#34;300px&#34; align=&#34;right&#34; src=&#34;https://scontent-ams2-1.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-xta1/t31.0-8/12094781_914998871870460_7303528174420982861_o.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was about the age of 11 when my older brother went to college and he made a mini version of Pokémon. It made me interested in how he did it. So he told me I had to look at JavaScript. From that moment on my life changed. I began to search on the internet and I found some tutorials that gave me a basic insight. When I had learned the basics I wanted to learn more so I decided to go for IT management in secondary school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My whole life is about IT. When I come home from school I turn on my pc and it stays on till I go to sleep. That’s about 8 hours a day, I know it’s pretty much but I think that IT is and will be the future. Most of the time when I’m on my pc I’m playing video games. But for school I also need my pc. Most of our homework is online like all our GIP assignments. I often think about making a network at home but I haven’t found the right time yet. I also play a lot of different games like League of Legends, Minecraft, Counterstrike, etc&amp;hellip; I don’t often make a website because I’m not so good with designs but when I have to do it I can make a decent site. When I play some games or use a program I’m always fascinated with how they make something. Sometimes I even try to find out what language they used and try it out myself. I don’t think I’m a pro but I can say that I’m an advanced programmer in the early stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the future I hope to learn more and more about different things in the IT world, not only programming but also some system management. My ambitions are to become a pretty good hacker but not for the illegal stuff. Maybe if I have the chance, become a hacker for the state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think there has been a big evolution in my programming skills. When I first began to program with C# I was happy I could make a program to print some text. Now I’m happy that I can make a whole game in C# or another language.
IT has become a really important part of my life. Like one day my keyboard didn’t work anymore and didn’t have a spare one. I couldn’t make my homework, so I had nothing to do. I don’t think I could live without my pc for a month.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workflow: Hugo vs WordPress</title>
      <link>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/artikels/Software/GIP_Taak_07/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 18:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/artikels/Software/GIP_Taak_07/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Hugo is een programma dat werkt met het implementeeren van codes terwijl Wordpress werkt met een drag and drop systeem. Daardoor is Wordpress veel makkelijker en beter om mee te starten. Hugo daar in tegen is een veel moeilijker programma want daar moet je alle code zelf gaan implenteren. Doordat de documentie niet zo denderend is is het ook zeer moeilijk om hier aan te beginnen. Nu we alle nadelen hebben besproken van Hugo zijn er ook een paar voordelen. Het sterke punt van hugo is dat je heel gamakkelijk je post kan maken en aanpassen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;een-overzicht-van-de-directory-structuur:e12a4ef27342a56a1ab334ac45819bd3&#34;&gt;Een overzicht van de directory-structuur&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;links:e12a4ef27342a56a1ab334ac45819bd3&#34;&gt;links&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/jens-vanhoof/GIP&#34;&gt;Gitlab&lt;/a&gt; -
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jens-vanhoof/GIP&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt; -
&lt;a href=&#34;http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/  &#34;&gt;Public&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;content:e12a4ef27342a56a1ab334ac45819bd3&#34;&gt;Content&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hierin komen alle post die worden aangemaakt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;layouts:e12a4ef27342a56a1ab334ac45819bd3&#34;&gt;Layouts&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;index.html: Dit zorgt voor mijn home page en gebruikt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;partials : Hierin staan bijna alle elementen die ik gebruik in mijn site bv elke pagina die       ik maak gebruik de header.html en footer.html.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;default : Deze map wordt gebruikt als er in partails geen gepaste file bevind dat hugo nodig heeft gebruikt het deze files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;static:e12a4ef27342a56a1ab334ac45819bd3&#34;&gt;Static&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hierin bevinden zich de css en javascript files van de site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;rest:e12a4ef27342a56a1ab334ac45819bd3&#34;&gt;Rest&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Config.toml: Hierin kan je verschillende veriablen declareren die je met hugo kan aanroepen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>