<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engels on GIP site</title>
    <link>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/categories/engels/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engels on GIP site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 14:46:35 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/categories/engels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>IT-autobiography</title>
      <link>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/artikels/Engels/IT-autobiography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 14:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jens-vanhoof.github.io/GIP/artikels/Engels/IT-autobiography/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My name is Jens Van Hoof, a 17-year old! student at the Immaculata institute in Oostmalle. Currently I&amp;rsquo;m studying IT-management. Most of the time, I&amp;rsquo;m the guy who helps people who don&amp;rsquo;t get it yet. Later I want to be a programmer of software or games. My dream job is to be a hacker for the state.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width=&#34;400px&#34; height=&#34;300px&#34; align=&#34;right&#34; src=&#34;https://scontent-ams2-1.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-xta1/t31.0-8/12094781_914998871870460_7303528174420982861_o.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was about the age of 11 when my older brother went to college and he made a mini version of Pokémon. It made me interested in how he did it. So he told me I had to look at JavaScript. From that moment on my life changed. I began to search on the internet and I found some tutorials that gave me a basic insight. When I had learned the basics I wanted to learn more so I decided to go for IT management in secondary school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My whole life is about IT. When I come home from school I turn on my pc and it stays on till I go to sleep. That’s about 8 hours a day, I know it’s pretty much but I think that IT is and will be the future. Most of the time when I’m on my pc I’m playing video games. But for school I also need my pc. Most of our homework is online like all our GIP assignments. I often think about making a network at home but I haven’t found the right time yet. I also play a lot of different games like League of Legends, Minecraft, Counterstrike, etc&amp;hellip; I don’t often make a website because I’m not so good with designs but when I have to do it I can make a decent site. When I play some games or use a program I’m always fascinated with how they make something. Sometimes I even try to find out what language they used and try it out myself. I don’t think I’m a pro but I can say that I’m an advanced programmer in the early stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the future I hope to learn more and more about different things in the IT world, not only programming but also some system management. My ambitions are to become a pretty good hacker but not for the illegal stuff. Maybe if I have the chance, become a hacker for the state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think there has been a big evolution in my programming skills. When I first began to program with C# I was happy I could make a program to print some text. Now I’m happy that I can make a whole game in C# or another language.
IT has become a really important part of my life. Like one day my keyboard didn’t work anymore and didn’t have a spare one. I couldn’t make my homework, so I had nothing to do. I don’t think I could live without my pc for a month.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>